{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622893","name":"Lighthouse Fish Market & Grocery","address":"15391 Schaefer Rd","zipcode":"48227","owner":"Mufaid H-M","licenseNumber":"237164","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.17958,42.40365","geojson":{"id":"51622893","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.179583192,42.403645741]},"properties":{"name":"Lighthouse Fish Market & Grocery","owner":"Mufaid H-M","address":"15391 Schaefer Rd","zipcode":"48227","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"237164","establishmentid":"51622893","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"5/18/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5175","name":"Gunny Ray's Shrimp & Chicken","address":"15391 Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"1214","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #964","address":"13531 Fenkell Ave","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"5393","name":"Five Hundred Degrees","address":"15090 Schaefer","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"1866","name":"Lee's Texas Style Bar-B-Que","address":"14001 Fenkell Ave","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"1873","name":"Suite 100","address":"15789 Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"782","name":"Toya's Bar & Grill","address":"14906 Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"4164","name":"Disabled Am. Vets K-R Metro Chp. No.1","address":"13221 Puritan Ave","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"766","name":"Akbar's Coffee Shop","address":"12943 Fenkell Ave","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"852","name":"John R King Academic & Performing Arts ","address":"15850 Strathmoor St","zipcode":"48227"},{"establishmentid":"5400","name":"Hubbell Fish & Chicken","address":"14535 Fenkell","zipcode":"48227"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49240","inspectionDate":"2019-09-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48665","inspectionDate":"2019-08-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.11","violationDescription":"A) A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be designed, constructed, and installed according to LAW*. (P)\r\nB) A PLUMBING FIXTURE such as a HANDWASHING SINK, toilet, or urinal shall be EASILY CLEANABLE. \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-301.15","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands in a HANDWASHING SINK or APPROVED automatic handwashing facility and may not clean their hands in a sink used for FOOD preparation or WAREWASHING, or in a service sink or a curbed cleaning facility used for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Employee washed/rinsed hands","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In three compartment sink","subProblem":"","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-502.11","violationDescription":"REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables shall be removed from the PREMISES at a frequency that will minimize the development of objectionable odors and other conditions that attract or harbor insects and rodents.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pick up frequency for refuse","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44847","inspectionDate":"2019-01-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With ledges, projections, or crevices","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622893"}}